[{"answer": "No, I haven't.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Have you ever seen anything like this in your lifetime?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, listen, today people are devastated and so my job today is to let people know that I understand how they feel, I share their feelings, but that we've got to suck it up and move on.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "How do you rally them, how are they reacting on the ground?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Have you found it a very emotional day since you've seen what's been going on?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, listen, this is going to be a difficult week.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "What should they be doing when they watch this tomorrow, the next day and so on, for the rest of this week?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, first off, you give them a hug and you say don't be scared, mom and dad will protect you.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What does any parent say to a child when this kind of catastrophe happens on their doorstep?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "I think they look at their children and, you know, children are obviously scared about this.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "What would you say -- what does a parent say, what should parents be telling their kids in New Jersey now?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Not quite yet.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Have you worked out yet where you intend taking him?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "But did anything really prepare you for this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Yes, I spoke to Governor Romney on -- I think that was either Saturday night or Sunday night, Piers.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Have you had a chance to speak to Governor Romney?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I'm doing all right, obviously we're dealing with a lot of challenges statewide.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Mr. Mayor, how are you?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Well, look, you know, they hear it on the front lines of this crisis, where you see he emergency workers reaching out to residents, where I've seen cooperation between port authority police, my fire department.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, that's the crisis.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "And what are you hearing about people who may be trapped or areas where these services have simply not been able to get to them?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Yes, it really is.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "They were saying 80 homes but I believe it's nearer 100, is that right?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "And we still don't know if the cause was a power line that had been downed or a transformer, is that right?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "A lot of people were evacuated.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Do you think that will stay the case, that everyone got out, there's no one's died here?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Well, I think we -- by great team work and by really focusing on patients' safety, all of the children were transported safely and made it to the receiving hospitals without any incident, which is what we were intending to do.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "How are they all doing is the obvious question now, I guess?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I have to say this is the first time, but we have highly trained staff.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Have you ever had anything like this?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Are you confident now that everyone's going to be OK as a result of all the moving that went on last night?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "First, before I answer that, let me just say how proud I am to work for NYU Langone Medical Center, where we have physicians like Dr. Rudy and staff and nurses and volunteers and the New York City Fire Department and Police Department, who did an extraordinary effort in incredibly difficult circumstances, evacuating all our patients in 12 hours safely.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "The obvious question, it seemed to me last night, remains so now, is how could a busy New York hospital have its backup generators fail when it's had a week at least to prepare for what everyone was saying was going to be a storm of huge magnitude?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, I really didn't come on to talk about the generators.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "I mean, is there some big investigation going on now?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "They failed.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "but they weren't working, were they?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "They started working.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "If they failed, they're not working, are they?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "UBIN: Well, again, I'm not an engineer and I'm not really here to talk about the generators.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "The question I would want to know from the hospital, if I was involved in any way, is how do you have any confidence this won't happen again?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "I'm OK.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Christine, how are you?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "We spoke last night in the middle of all this mayhem.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "How are you guys doing?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I think there are obviously enormous questions that NYU needs to answer.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "What do you think of this?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "My understanding was that's on a list of questions to be answered, too, right, as we get into the next couple of days.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "I just got that notification as well, that JFK and -- excuse me, JFK and Newark will partially open tomorrow and that Laguardia is still flooded.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Have you heard that?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "So how and why do you think this happened?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "You bought a house six months ago which has been lost to the flooding, is that right?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Well, we're going to try to figure this out in the next couple days.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "How does it work in reality?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Well, we have to see how the cleanup goes, and if Obama makes a mistake later on.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "That has to be good for him, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Well, this is why we give probabilities.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "What happens to pollster experts like you?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "ILVER: It's too early to say, because a number of the more reputable pollsters suspended their polling because of the hurricane.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Are you seeing anything in any polls in the last 24 hours -- have there been any, in fact, which suggest that the hurricane as a disaster has had any impact yet?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "It's kind of wobbling and spinning down right now.", "docId": "121030pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Is it easy to predict over the next, say, 36 hours?", "qSentId": 573}]